(Sheldon:)What a wonderful day, thank you.
(Penny:)Oh, we're glad
you had fun.
(Sheldon:)Blue Icees and a trip
to The Container Store?
(Sheldon:)It's like I died and went
to the post-mortem,
(Sheldon:)neuron-induced hallucination
commonly mistaken as heaven.
(Leonard:)I still don't understand
why you bought that pill caddie.
(Leonard:)You're a young man.
(Sheldon:)Age is a state of
mind, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)In here I'm 90.
(Sheldon:)Why are you taking
your bins over there?
That's just where
I need them.
(Leonard:)You know, she doesn't have
a lot of closet space.
(Sheldon:)What's wrong with your closet?
(Penny:)Uh...
(Penny:)Well, honey, you know,
(Penny:)now that Leonard and I
are married,
(Penny:)it kind of makes sense
that we actually live together.
(Sheldon:)So that's all this day was?
(Sheldon:)A plan to butter me up
before delivering bad news?
(Leonard:)Come on, buddy.
No, I thought we were friends.
(Sheldon:)You asked for a sip of my Icee.
(Sheldon:)If you had your own straw,
I might've said yes.
(Penny:)Sheldon, please, we already
feel bad about this.
(Sheldon:)You know what they don't sell
at The Container Store?
(Sheldon:)Something large enough
to contain my disappointment.
(Sheldon:)Although,
(Sheldon:)if anyone did, it would be them.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪